westerracu.com 2019-03-24

# Westerra Credit Union Privacy Notice

Westerra Credit Union Privacy Notice Revised 12/16
FACTS: What does Westerra Credit Union (“Westerra”) do with your personal information?
                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                   gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
Why?
                   us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read
                   this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service
                   you have with us. This information can include:
What?                 •     Social Security number and income              •     Credit history and credit scores
                      •     Account balances and payment history
                   All ﬁnancial companies need to share members personal information to run their everyday
                   business. In the section below, we list the reasons ﬁnancial companies can share their
How?               customers’ personal information; the reasons Westerra chooses to share; and whether you
                   can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal                                   Does Westerra             Can You Limit This
information                                                          Share?                    Sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to
process your transactions, maintain in your account(s),
                                                                             Yes                         No
respond to court orders and legal investigations, or
report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes - to offer products and
                                                                             Yes                         Yes
services to you
For joint marketing with other ﬁnancial companies                            Yes                         Yes
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                                                             No                   We do not share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                                                             No                   We do not share
information about your creditworthiness
For our afﬁliates’ to market to you                                          No                   We do not share
For our non-afﬁliates’ to market to you                                      No                   We do not share
                         >> Call 303-321-4209 or 1-800-858-7212 to speak with a ﬁnancial services representative.
                         >> Please note:
To Limit                 If you are a new member we can begin sharing your information 30 days from
Our Sharing              the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue
                         to share your information as described in this notice.
                         However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?               Call 303-321-4209 or 1-800-858-7212
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?                 Westerra Credit Union (“Westerra”)
What we do
                                              To protect your personal information from an unauthorized access
                                              and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                              These measures include computer safeguards and secured ﬁles
How does Westerra protect
                                              and buildings. We limit collection and use of non-public personal
my personal information?
                                              information to the minimum required. We maintain physical,
                                              electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal
                                              and state standards
                                              We collect your personal information, for example, when you
                                                    >> Open an account or deposit money
How does Westerra collect                           >> Pay your bills or apply for a loan
my personal information?                            >> Use your credit or debit card
                                              We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                              credit bureaus, afﬁliates or other companies.
                                              Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                    >> Sharing for afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                                          information about your creditworthiness
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                      >> Afﬁliates from using your information to market to you
                                                    >> Sharing for non-afﬁliates to market to you
                                              State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                              rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit
                                              Your choices will apply to everyone on your account - unless you
sharing for an account I hold
                                              tell us otherwise.
jointly with someone else?
Deﬁnitions
                            Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be ﬁnancial and
                            nonﬁnancial companies.
Afﬁliates
                            >> Our afﬁliates include companies with the “Westerra” or “Westerra Credit
                                 Union name that are under common control with us.
                            Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be ﬁnancial and
                            nonﬁnancial companies.
                            >> Non-afﬁliates we share with include government entities in response to
Non-Afﬁliates                    subpoenas and other legal processes, credit bureaus, mortgage
                                 companies, companies providing servicing, processing, accounting, or
                                 similar types of functions, companies originating loans or loan
                                 applications, and insurance companies.
                            A formal agreement between non-afﬁliated ﬁnancial companies that together
Joint
                            market ﬁnancial products or services to you.
Marketing
                            >> Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
Other Important Information
None
                                                           • 35 •
